travelpickr.com 2018-05-13

# Travelpickr - Find your Personal Trip Planner

  * The details...

  * What it means...

  * ### Privacy Commitment

Your privacy is very important to Travelpickr Inc, and so we take the responsibility of protecting your privacy very seriously. Most importantly, we will never share or sell your personal details to any third parties you have not purchased tours from on travelpickr.com ("the site"). This policy explains how we use the information collected on the site. Please read it before submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Your privacy is super important to us. We will never sell your personal info!**

  * ### Collection of Information

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, phone numbers, etc. ("your information"), when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request, including the booking of tours sold on Travelpickr, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner. It is necessary you provide your contact information to signup and purchase tours.

**We need your contact details to book tours.**

  * ### Cookie/Tracking Technology

The site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Cookies are good. They make the site do cool stuff.**

  * ### Distribution of Information

Your information will never be shared with tour operators you have not purchased tours from on Travelpickr. It may be shared with tour operators from whom you have purchased tours. It may be required for them to fulfill the service you have requested, and may be used to contact you about this service. Tour operators are bound by the site terms which state that they may only contact you only about the tour you bought, and only if absolutely necessary. They must also follow the same privacy policy by agreeing not to give your information to other parties (Any tour operator not abiding by these policies and rules should be reported to Travelpickr staff, and will face account suspension, and legal action may be taken against them). Travelpickr will never share your information with any other third parties who are not part of the Travelpickr family of brands. We do employ other companies and persons to perform certain business functions on our behalf, including but not limited to website development and maintenance, marketing, accounting and payment processing. These third parties have access to user information needed to perform their functions, but they may not use it for any other purposes.

**We do not give your info to anyone! Except maybe a tour operator you bought a tour from.**

  * ### Legal Purposes

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. We may disclose your information if required to do so pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants, and orders, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, notwithstanding any terms to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we retain the right to use, disclose and/or share your personal and non-personal information to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person.

**We obey the law like all good boys and girls.**

  * ### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, tour operators and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. You may request the closure of your account at any time to prevent your information from being viewed by you, or anyone, with your password when logging into the site.

**We will keep your data in a really big cyber vault**

  * **You can ask us anything. Really**
